<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-08-21T13:41:39+08:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Your awesome title</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">MetaDiffuser: Diffusion Model as Conditional Planner for Offline Meta-RL</title><link href="/2023/08/02/MetaDiffuser.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="MetaDiffuser: Diffusion Model as Conditional Planner for Offline Meta-RL" /><published>2023-08-02T05:53:35+08:00</published><updated>2023-08-02T05:53:35+08:00</updated><id>/2023/08/02/MetaDiffuser</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2023/08/02/MetaDiffuser.html"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, diffusion model shines as a promising backbone for the sequence modeling paradigm in offline reinforcement learning. However, these works mostly lack the generalization ability across tasks with reward or dynamics change. To tackle this challenge, in this paper we propose a task-oriented conditioned diffusion planner for offline meta-RL(MetaDiffuser), which considers the generalization problem as conditional trajectory generation task with contextual representation. The key is to learn a context conditioned diffusion model which can generate task-oriented trajectories for planning across diverse tasks. To enhance the dynamics consistency of the generated trajectories while encouraging trajectories to achieve high returns, we further design a dual-guided module in the sampling process of the diffusion model. The proposed framework enjoys the robustness to the quality of collected warm-start data from the testing task and the flexibility to incorporate with different task representation method. The experiment results on MuJoCo benchmarks show that MetaDiffuser outperforms other strong offline meta-RL baselines, demonstrating the outstanding conditional generation ability of diffusion architecture.]]></summary></entry></feed>